leadsmarket.com 2012-05-22

# LeadsMarket.com - Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the LeadsMarket.com website (the "Website"). This websites is an Internet properties of LeadsMarket.com LLC ("LeadsMarket.com," "we" or "us"). LeadsMarket.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our visitor's personally identifiable information. To better protect your privacy, we provide this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is used at our Websites. By visiting the Websites, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your Personal Information to any third party for marketing purposes, please e-mail us at: support@LeadsMarket.com. Please be advised that where California residents opt-out from permitting their Personal Information to be shared, such individuals may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with the law. 

What Information We Collect and How We Use It

Personally Identifiable Information

The Websites comprise an online marketing network that allows advertisers and affiliates to enter into mutually beneficial marketing relationships. To accomplish this, interested parties must complete the applicable agreement(s) with LeadsMarket.com ("Agreements"). In order to complete the Agreement(s), applicants must supply certain personally identifiable information. The Websites also may collect personal information in connection with: (a) your completion of a survey, order form or registration page; (ii) your communications with LeadsMarket.com and/or the Websites; and (iii) information from third parties as set forth in the "Supplementation of Information" Section below. The personally identifiable information that we collected may include, but is not limited to: (i) full name; (ii) complete mailing address; (iii) e-mail address; (iv) daytime, evening and mobile telephone numbers; (v) date of birth; (vi) gender; (vii) education status; (viii) marital status; (ix) occupation; (x) salary range; (xi) employment information; (xii) Social Security Number; (xiii) credit card and ID verification information, such as credit card number; and (xiv) such other information that we may request from time to time. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, the information described in (x) through (xiii) above, and any other financial information requested of you, shall be considered "Sensitive Information." We collect this personal information only from those individuals/entities that choose to participate.

We use this information to process requests for products and services. We also use collected information to communicate with you, such as to notify you (through e-mails and newsletters) about updates to products, to send you order confirmations and/or to provide you with important product warranty or safety information.

In addition, we use the personal information that you provide, other than your Sensitive Information, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you, by means of e-mail or through our newsletter, additional products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

Supplementation of Information 

We may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect online with outside records (e.g., information from our affiliates, subsidiaries and third party partners (collectively, "Strategic Partners") or from wireless providers) to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

Sharing of Your Information

Agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect it in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for LeadsMarket.com.

In addition, if you access the Website(s) through third-party website(s), such as one of our Strategic Partners' websites, we also may need to report certain personally identifiable information (e.g., name and e-mail address) back to that referring website(s). As we explain in the following Section, we will tell you at the point of collection if we will share personally identifiable information with the Strategic Partner through which you access the Website(s).

In addition, we will share aggregated demographic information with our Strategic Partners. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

We will never disclose any credit card information to any third-party marketers or other non-governmental entity. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may: (a) share the fact that we have credit card information on file for specific users of the Website(s) but we will not share your specific credit card information with such third parties without your prior informed consent; (b) share your credit card information with consumer credit agencies; and (c) disclose your credit card information to third party processors for the sole purpose of effectuating transactions that you enter into at the Website(s). We may also disclose your personally identifiable and/or Sensitive Information: (i) to a governmental entity if so ordered by a court of law, to comply with the local, state and federal laws (ii) where otherwise required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Website(s); or (iii) if we are sold or acquired.

Our Collection of Personally Identifiable Information Through a Third-party Website

To provide you with content and service, we have relationships with many of the best service and content companies. As a result of these relationships, you can access the Website(s) through third-party websites. You can recognize most of the LeadsMarket.com pages on these third-party websites by looking for the joint branding of LeadsMarket.com and a third-party company. For example, if you see a logo on the page that says "Powered by LeadsMarket.com" you are most likely on a co-branded page. 

Whenever you provide registration information on a co-branded page, that data may be shared with the third-party website through which you access the Website(s). If personally identifiable information may be provided to such a third party, we will inform you at the point of collection and provide you with an opportunity to tell us not to share your personally identifiable information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of such third parties, as this Privacy Policy does not cover their use of information. 

Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about our visitors when you visit many of our Website pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows '98 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink). 

We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our Website pages and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Website usage.

Choices/Opt Out 

If you prefer not to receive marketing information from us or wish to fully deactivate your account information, simply let us know by sending a letter via certified mail to 6130 Elton Avenue Suite # 386, Las Vegas, NV 89107  
To opt out from the newsletter, you can unsubscribe your email by visiting our unsubscribe page. or an e-mail to Customer Relations. Please note that even if you chose to opt out of LeadsMarket.com’s marketing, we will continue to send you important service-related communications (e.g., order confirmation or product safety information). However, these communications will not be promotional in nature. 

Cookies

To enhance your experience with the Website(s), we use "cookies." Cookies are used by your computer's browser to store your preferences. We use both session and persistent cookies. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information.

We use cookies to understand Website usage and to improve the content and offerings on the Website(s). You can disable cookies through your Internet browser. If you set your browser not to accept cookies, you will still be able to use the Website(s). To find out more about cookies, please visit www.cookiecentral.com.

Web Beacons

A web beacon is a programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page, but can also be used to transfer your unique user identification to a database and associate you with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows LeadsMarket.com to track certain websites that you visit. Web beacons are used to track LeadsMarket.com behavioral habits for marketing purposes to determine products or services that you may be interested in. In addition to using web beacons on web pages, LeadsMarket.com also uses web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in LeadsMarket.com’s database. 

New Technology  
The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly developing. As a result, LeadsMarket.com strongly encourages individuals to revisit this Privacy Policy for any updates regarding its use of new technology.

Links  
In addition, the Website(s) contain(s) links to other websites whose information practices may be different than ours. Our Privacy Policy does not cover these third parties' use of information. Visitors should consult the other companies' and websites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

No Information Collected from Children  
We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children. LeadsMarket.com will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of eighteen (18). If LeadsMarket.com obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of eighteen (18), that information will be immediately deleted from its database. Because it does not collect such information, LeadsMarket.com has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. LeadsMarket.com has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children’s Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). 

Security  
All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. When our registration/application process prompts users to enter Sensitive Information, and when we store and transmit such Sensitive Information, that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. While we use SSL encryption to protect Sensitive Information online, we also do everything in our power to protect other user information both online and off-line. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. All of our users’ information, not just Sensitive Information, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personal information. Furthermore, access to this information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all user information. Employees not adhering to our firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. Please note that any attempt to breach the security of the network, our servers, databases or other hardware or software supporting the Website(s) or other websites under the control of LeadsMarket.com constitutes a crime punishable by law. We will turn over to authorities, any and all evidence relating to a potential breach of security or other abuse against the network, servers, databases or other such supporting equipment or software. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

Reviewing Your Information  
If you would like to review and update or correct the personally identifiable information that we have collected from you, or if no longer wish to continue your service with us, simply send your request via certified mail to 6130 Elton Avenue Suite # 386, Las Vegas, NV 89107. You may also send your request via e-mail to Customer Relations.  
To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

California User Consumer Rights 

In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080 , Sacramento , CA 95814 ; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov. 

For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: www.ftc.gov. 

If you have questions about this policy, please contact us at support@LeadsMarket.com.

Notification of Changes  
LeadsMarket.com reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice on our Website(s) that we are changing our Privacy Policy. If the manner in which we use personally identifiable information changes, LeadsMarket.com will notify you by: (a) posting the changes as a start-up screen prior to your subsequent use of the products and/or service offered on the Website(s); (b) sending the modified policy to the users via e-mail; (c) placing a link to the modified policy on the applicable Website’s home page; or (d) by any other reasonable means acceptable under applicable state and federal law. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. At any time that you do not agree with the changes, you must opt out from receiving future communications from us (see the "Choices/Opt-Out" section above). Failure to opt out after notice of any such changes constitutes an affirmative acknowledgement and acceptance by you of the modified Privacy Policy. 

Contact Us  
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at: support@LeadsMarket.com
